http://www.g-star.com/en_us/help-info/privacy-policy

Press enter to go to our contact page or call customer service directly through 888-933-3301
Cyprus
Czech Rep.
Continue
Your bag will be emptied when you change your country settings.
Translate the website
We currently only provide our site in English for your country. Do you want to translate it to Danish with Google Translate?
Sustainable Collection
Where is it made?
About G-Star RAW
Where is my order?
PRIVACY STATEMENT OF G-STAR
1. Does this Privacy statement apply to you?
2. What personal data does G-Star process and for which purpose?
3. Who has access to your personal data?
4. How long will G-Star keep your personal data?
5. What measures does G-Star take to protect your personal data?
6. Does G-Star collects data of children?
7. What rights can you exercise in relation to your personal data?
8. What if you have other questions or complaints?
9. Will there be updates to this Privacy statement?
PRIVACY STATEMENT OF G-STAR
Date: 01/09/2019
G-Star Raw C.V., G-Star eStore B.V., Erno’s B.V.
and their operating groups, subsidiaries and divisions (hereafter “G-Star”, “We” or “Us”) are committed to the privacy and security of your personal data. This Privacy Statement explains what personal data We collect, how We use and protect it, and your respective rights.
Contact information
G-Star Raw eStore Inc.
New York, NY 10012, USA
888-933-3301
service.us@g-star.com
www.g-star.com
For the contact details of our operating groups, subsidiaries and divisions, please see here.
Overview
The following questions and answers explain how G-Star processes your personal data:
1. Does this Privacy statement apply to you?
2. What personal data does G-Star process and for which purpose?
3. Who has access to your personal data?
4. How long will G-Star keep your personal data?
5. What measures does G-Star take to protect your personal data?
6. Does G-Star collects data of children?
7. What rights can you exercise in relation to your personal data?
8. What if you have other questions or complaints?
9. Will there be updates to this Privacy statement?
1. Does this Privacy statement apply to you?
This Privacy statement applies to you if you:
are a customer of G-Star;
have a subscription to the G-Star newsletter or participate in a promotional activity of G-Star;
visit the website of G-Star (www.g-star.com) or one of the underlying sub-pages (“Website”);
visit a G-Star store.
are accepting #YESGStar. Please consult our Flowbox privacy statement for more information.
2. What personal data does G-Star process and for which purpose?
In the course of its business activities, G-Star processes personal data. “Personal Data” is any information that can directly or indirectly be used to identify a natural person. You provide most of your personal data voluntarily to us. In some cases, the personal data is collected automatically by G-Star or obtained from a third party source. G-Star will process personal data if:
a. You are a customer of G-Star
G-Star processes customers’ personal data to sell its products. This involves entry into a sales agreement to process your payment and, where relevant, to ship your product to you. Processing necessarily includes application of security, fraud prevention, and credit checks and registration.
G- Star processes the following customer personal data:
Contact information, including your name, (invoice and delivery) address, e-mail address and phone number;
Personal information, including your date of birth and preferences;
Order information, including product, size, payment method, shipping method, order history;
Financial information, including your bank account number, credit card number, invoice specifications, order amount, payment status;
Optional information, such as your gender, company information and account details.
As a customer, you also have the option to make use of the following related services:
Account: to optimize and simplify your shopping experience, you can create an account on the Webiste. In order to create your Account, G-Star will process your:
Contact information, including your name, address, e-mail address and phone number;
Account information, including your e-mail address and password.
Optional information, such as your gender, date of birth and company information; and your preferences, including your preferred store, product categories and size.
Customer Service:
For questions or complaints regarding G-Star products or services, you may contact G-Star customer service at 888-933-3301 and https://www.g-star.com/en_us/customer-service/contact. Before G-Star can process your question or complaint, G-Star will need to verify your identity based on your personal data which may include:
Contact information, including your name, address, e-mail address, age, gender, data of birth, nationality and phone number;
Content, including the subject of the message, remarks, images and screenshots, the content of the telephone conversation;
Optional information, such as order number.
G-Star uses this personal data for the following purposes:
To better perform our obligations under our agreement with you;
To help you have the best customer experience with Us.
To remember your language and other preferences;
To help you obtain information you need;
To provide a safe and secure means of transacting business with Us;
To evaluate and improve our level of customer satisfaction and to better understand our customers; and
To fulfill legal obligations or exercise legal rights of G-Star, its affiliates, or other third-parties.
b.
You have a subscription to the G-Star newsletter, participate in a G-Star promotional activity
or participate in the G-Star loyalty program
G-Star Newsletter: G-Star would like to keep you informed of news relating to G-Star and send you special offers. If necessary we will ask your consent before sending you our newsletters and offers. To send you our newsletter, G-Star processes the following information:
Contact information, including your name, address, e-mail address, age, gender, data of birth, nationality, phone number, Social Media details;
Order information, including order history, preference history, products in basket;
Preferences, including preferred store (location), size;
Technical information, including subscriber key, account type, customer sentiment.
If you have indicated your preferences in your account, we will tailor our communication to what we think you will be interested in and provide you with personalized offers. Each communication will include an opt-out link to allow you to unsubscribe from the newsletter. You may also adjust your preferences in your account.
Promotional activity: G-star may also organize a promotional activity in which you may participate. To conduct the promotional activity, including for instance to select a winner and communicate the results, G-Star may require the following information:
Contact information, including your name, address, e-mail address, age, gender, data of birth, nationality and phone number;
Promotional information, including the content you provide in order to participate in the promotional activity;
Technical information, including a promotional code.
Loyalty program: You can subscribe to the G-Star loyalty program on the Website or in a G-Star store. To subscribe to the loyalty program, you’ll need to provide the following information:
Email address;
Gender
Optional information, such as first and last name, date of birth, sizes, and product preferences.
Upon successfully subscribing to the G-Star loyalty program, your Website account will change into a G-Star reward account. In this account, you can view the following information, which G-Star will use to provide you with loyalty program rewards:
Personal information, including shipping information, your birthday and your sizes;
Member card number
Points / status (benefits of status, point history, FAQ)
Personal styling service (silver, gold & platinum)
Vouchers
Opt-in settings for marketing & membership
Online / offline purchases
Refer a friend settings and history
G-Star uses this personal data for the following purposes:
To perform our obligations under our agreement with you;
To identify you when you subscribe;
To administer and manage your Account;
To provide information about and to deliver our rewards program, customized advertising, communications and content from us specific to your interests;
To help you obtain information you are looking for;
To provide a safe and secure service and enhanced customer experience;
To measure effectiveness of our loyalty program, how you use it, and to better understand you as well as other members;
To respond to your questions and requests; and
To fulfill legal obligations or exercise legal rights of G-Star, its affiliates, or other third-parties.
c.
You visit the Website
By visiting the Website, G-Star automatically collects information by means of cookies and similar technologies. This information may consist of:
Identifiers, including IP-address, cookie-id or device-id;
Information about your connection to the website, webpages and/or the ad server, including the date, time and type of the connection;
Internet browser details, including browser type and language settings;
Operating system details, including OS type and language settings;
Device details, including location and (in case of mobile device) longitude, latitude, model and carrier;
Use of and interaction with the website, webpage or advertisement, including your interests and click-trail;
Information on the advertisements presented to you;
Social Media details, such as account details.
Your activities over time and across third-party websites, apps, or other online services
c.
You visit the Website
To learn more about the use of these technologies, please consult our Cookie Statement.
The major browsers have attempted to implement the draft “Do Not Track” (“DNT”) standard of the World Wide Web Consortium (“W3C”) in their latest releases. As this standard has not been finalized, the G-Star site is not compatible with DNT.
G-Star uses this personal data for the following purposes:
To perform our obligations under our agreement with you;
To help us and third parties obtain information about your visits to the Website;
To analyze your use of the Website to improve our Website;
To deliver advertising, communications and content from us and third parties, on our Website and those of third parties, specific to your interests;
To remember your language and other preferences;
To help you obtain information you are looking for;
To provide a safe and secure service and transactions;
To measure how many people use our sites, and how they use them, to keep our sites running efficiently and to better understand our audiences;
To secure, amend and improve our Website;
To secure the G-Star system by enhancing the security controls around platform access;
To provide your information to third parties in accordance with this Privacy Statement; and
To fulfill legal obligations or exercise legal rights of G-Star, its affiliates, or other third-parties.
We will analyze your information to build individual profiles. These profiles will be used to predict future interests and display targeted (online) advertisements. Our goal is to provide relevant and interesting offers to you. The profiling is based on your (surfing) behavior on the internet. This includes the viewing of advertisements, any interaction with it and the overlap between desktop and mobile usage.
d.
You visit a G-Star store
By visiting a G-Star owned and operated store, along with the categories of data above in section a, G-Star may process your personal data for the following purposes:
Protecting rights and security. In order to protect the rights and security of our organization, employees and visitors and in order to investigate crimes or violations of our policies G-Star will process the following personal data:
Video images.
Improving product and services In order to improve our products and services, for example by counting the number of visitors to G-Star stores and optimizing the lay-out of products in G-Star stores, G-Star may process the following personal data:
First and last name;
E-mail address;
Identifiers such as your MAC address or IP address;
Time and location of your visit to a G-Star store.
Newsletter Subscription. When you visit a G-Star store, you may be provided the opportunity to subscribe to our newsletter. When you subscribe, G-Star may process the following personal data:
First and last name;
E-mail address;
3. Who has access to your personal data?
G-Star may:
Share your personal data with its affiliates, operating groups, subsidiaries and divisions, or with third parties if such is necessary for the purposes as listed above. G-Star will require third parties to conduct activities in a manner consistent with G-Star policies and guidelines in relation to data protection.
Share your personal data with parties processing personal data on our behalf. In such cases, these parties may only use your personal data for the purposes described above and only in accordance with our instructions. G-Star will only use parties which provide sufficient guarantees to implement appropriate technical and organizational measures and ensure the protection of your personal data.
Grant employees access to your personal data if necessary for the performance of their tasks. In such a case, access will be granted only if necessary for the purposes described above and only if the employee is bound by confidentiality.
Share your personal data if required to do so by law, court order, or other legal process, for example, with law enforcement agencies or other governmental agencies, to establish or exercise our legal rights or in connection with a corporate transaction, such as a divesture, merger, consolidation, or asset sale, or in the unlikely event of bankruptcy.
4. How long will G-Star keep your personal data?
G-Star retains your personal data in accordance to our record retention needs.
The exact period of time is based on the type of the personal data and the legal obligations or business purposes for retaining it. After the retention period, the personal data will be either destroyed or anonymized.
5. What measures does G-Star take to protect your personal data?
G-Star has taken appropriate technical and organizational security measures including, but not limited to, reasonable physical, electronic and managerial procedures designed to protect your personal data, all to ensure that:
your personal data is protected against unauthorized access;
the confidentiality of your personal data is assured;
the integrity and availability of your personal data will be maintained;
personnel is trained in information security requirements; and
actual or suspected data breaches are reported in accordance with applicable law.
Due to the nature of the Internet and related technology, We cannot absolutely guarantee the security of Personal Data, and We expressly disclaim any such obligation.
6. Does G-Star collects data of children?
G-Star does not knowingly collect, use or disclose Personal Data from anyone under the age of 13. If we determine upon collection that a user is under 13 years of age, we will not use or maintain his/her Personal Data without a parent/guardian's consent. If we become aware that we have unknowingly collected Personal Data from a child under the age of 13, we will make reasonable efforts to delete such information from our records.
7. What rights can you exercise in relation to your personal data?
Based on the law applicable to the use of your personal data, you may be able to exercise a number of rights in relation to your personal data. Note that in many cases, your rights are not absolute and We may not be required to comply with your request.
a. Your California Consumer Privacy Rights
Under California law, customers of G-Star who are California residents have certain rights regarding their personal data:
The California Civil Code Section 1798.83 requires any operator of a website to permit its California-resident customers to request and obtain from the operator a list of what personal information the operator disclosed to third parties for direct marketing purposes, for the preceding calendar year; and the addresses and names of such third parties. G-Star shares personal information collected with third parties for their direct marketing purposes. If you would like to receive a list of categories of personal information disclosed, you may forward your request to 888-933-3301 or send an e-mail to service.us@g-star.com.
The California Civil Code Section 1798.100 et seq., grants consumers various privacy rights to their personal information including:
Right of access. You have the right to request access to personal data that We collect. Please note that if your access request would require the disclosure of personal data of another individual, we would not be able to comply with all of your access request. Similarly, if responding to your access request would cause G-Star to violate any law, rule, regulation, or law enforcement request, we would also be unable to fulfill your request.
Right of deletion. You have the right to request that We delete personal data that We collected from you. However, We are not required to comply with your request if it is necessary for us or our service provider to maintain your personal data in order to complete the transaction with you, detect security incidences, identify and repair errors, exercise free speech, comply with the CA
Electronic Communications Privacy Act, engage in certain public interest research, use internally so long as reasonably aligned with your expectations, comply with a legal obligation or otherwise use your personal data internally so long as it is compatible with the context in which you provided it.
Right to opt-out. You have the right to opt-out of the sale of your personal data to third parties at any time. What this means is if you notify Us of your request, We will respect your wishes not to sell your personal data.
Right not to be discriminated for exercising these rights. You have the right to be free of discrimination for exercising your privacy rights. This means that We won’t deny you goods or services, charge different amounts or provide a different quality level of goods or services for exercising your rights unless the difference is reasonably related to the value of your data.
b. How to Exercise Your Rights:
In order to exercise your rights, you may submit a consumer privacy request by contacting Us at [our toll-free number, 888-933-3301 or send an e-mail to service.us@g-star.com ]
In order to opt out of G-Star’s sale of personal data to a third party click here where you will be directed to where you can make that choice.
8. What if you have other questions or complaints?
Questions or complaints regarding the processing of your personal data may be directed to G-Star by e-mail at service.us@g-star.com or by regular mail at 599 Broadway, 11th floor, New York, NY 10012, USA.
You may also call our toll-free number, 888-933-3301, Monday through Friday (from 8 AM to 8 PM EST) or Saturday (from 8 AM to 12 PM EST).
For the contact details of our operating groups, subsidiaries and divisions, please see here.
9. Will there be updates to this Privacy statement?
This Privacy Statement is effective as of 01-09-19. G-Star may update this Privacy Statement from time to time and will publish its updated Privacy Statement on its Website. Any such updated Privacy Statement is effective upon posting. We may also notify you via email or other direct electronic communication method of any changes that, in our sole discretion, materially impact treatment of your Personal Information. You are responsible for periodically visiting this Privacy Statement to check for changes. Your continued use of the Program is your acceptance of the Privacy Statement as revised. Identification of when the Privacy Statement has last been updated is located at the top left corner of the page.
Get insight in your personal data we gather to provide you with a relevant shopping experience.
Click here.
Print this page
Back to top
We use cookies.
Cookies are blocked or not supported by your browser. You must enable cookies to use this website.
